

Guilherme Amado da Silva

Full Stack Developer

Delft, Netherlands +31651452136 · amado.silva133@outlook.com

Github, Linkedin

Date / Place of birth 23/09/1998, Brasília

Nationality

Brazilian

Skills

Git JavaScript VueJS v2 VueJS v3 Vuetify VueX Typescript React Node.js **CSS** PHP Laravel Framework SQL MySQL Docker

Profile

Hi, I'm Guilherme! I'm a professional working in software development, currently focusing on front end and mobile but learning more about NodeJS in the backend. I'm always willing to learn new technologies

and I really like new challenges. My work is always focused on the user to have the best experience and interface while using the system. I'm always studying new technologies and also always wanting to expand my knowledge.

I worked in large companies like the Ministry of Health in Brazil, a research and technological innovation institute (FUNDEP) and also worked on the development of hybrid applications that have more than 20k users. So I always carry out my work with care and quality.

Nowadays I've been working abroad in The Netherlands. Here I'm able to improve my English skills but also to improve my coding knowledge.

Employment History

Frontend Developer, Turff, Delft

January 2022 — Present

Main activities: Develop frontend interfaces for multiple project using VueJS version 2, VueJS version 3, ReactJS and Typescript. After a while I started helping the backend that we mainly used NodeJS, Express and Typescript.

Projects: Dashboard (web.turff.nl), Delivery (delivery.turff.nl), Routing system used internally to manage the routes for the deliveries.

Development and Systems Analyst 1, Coopersystem, Brasília

July 2019 — December 2021

Main activities: Development in Frontend, using VueJS, Vuetify, Vuex e ReactJS technologies. Always focused in UX/UI. Developing big hybrid apps with more then 10k users.

Projects: IPEA Bolsas (ReactJS), Meu Clube (VueJS) and Voalá (ReactJS). Working for Bancorbrás as a client.

Junior Software Developer, FUNDEP/LABLIVRE, Brasília

Docker Compose
Responsive Layout
Flutter
Cypress
Heroku
Agile and Scrum
Fast Learner
Ability to Work in a Team
Ability to Work in a Team Multitasking Skills
Multitasking Skills
Multitasking Skills Cordova Languages

August 2018 — July 2019

Main activities: Development in PHP, VueJS, Vuetify, ZendFrameWork 1, Docker,

Docker Compose, open source software, Python and Lúmen.

Projects: Salic Lei Rouanet (https://github.com/culturagovbr/salic-minc),

Notification Service (https://github.com/culturagovbr/notification-service), Salic

Api and others.

Internships

Development Intern, Ministry of Culture, Brasília

August 2017 — August 2018

Main activities: Development in PHP, VueJS, ZendFrameWork 1, Docker, SQL

SERVER and Open Source Software.

Acting on the project Salic, culture incentive. (http://salic.cultura.gov.br)

Education

Bachelor in Systems Analysis and Development, UniCEUB, Brasília

January 2019 — July 2021

Degree in Systems Analysis and Development, is the profession dedicated to solving a problem through the tools available in the Information Technology universe.

Bachelor, University of Brasília, Brasília

January 2017 — May 2019

Degree in Computing at the University of Brasília. Course start 1/2017, Course locked due to start at UniCEUB University.

Graphic Designer Technician, SAGA ART OF ANIMATION, Brasília

January 2013 - February 2015

Extensive training in digital visual communication for the new generation, placing the student at the center of learning, stimulating creativity, technical and artistic improvement.

Tech Events

DarkMiraTour, Fortaleza

June 2019 - June 2019

PHP Experience, São Paulo

March 2019 - March 2019

Intercon, São Paulo

October 2018 — October 2018